J. D. Sloan Photographs MS247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic prints and negatives, 1978 -- 2013; MS247.001; 7.4 Linear Feet
  - Tufts 1994, MS247.001.002.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Tufts 1st Golden Key Induction, 1994-05-03; MS247.001.002.00004.00018 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940503-A to 940503-C
    - Tufts Dean Johansen Lab coat portrait, 1994-07-11; MS247.001.002.00004.00019 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940711-A to 940711-B
      Dean Johansen
    - Tufts: Dental Faculty Portraits, 1994-07-01; MS247.001.002.00004.00020 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940701-A to 940701-D
    - Non Threatening Dentistry emerge shoot, 1994-10-12; MS247.001.002.00004.00021 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941012-X to 941012-Z
      Marion Gaece
    - Mayer Ctr. HNRC Treadmill, labs etc, 1994-10-20; MS247.001.002.00004.00022 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941020-A to 941020-E
    - Center for Study of Drug Development post grad course, 1994-02-23; MS247.001.002.00004.00023 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940223-A to 940223-C
    - Tufts: Sackler Seminar, 1994-05-24; MS247.001.002.00004.00024 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940524-A to 940524-E
      Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences; Toni Snow
    - Tufts Dining, 1994-11-17; MS247.001.002.00004.00025 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941117-A to 941117-D
      Julie Lampi
    - Summer School Computers, 1994-05-04; MS247.001.002.00004.00026 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940504-Y to 940504-Z
    - Tufts Dental Solo, 1994-07-25; MS247.001.002.00004.00027 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940725
    - Tufts Employee Recognition, 1994-05-09; MS247.001.002.00004.00028 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940509-A to 940509-E
    - Shapiro Awards, 1994-04-20; MS247.001.002.00004.00029 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940420-A to 940420-C
    - Tufts:People's Republic of China Ambassador He Li Dayou, 1994-10-12; MS247.001.002.00004.00030 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941012-A to 941012-C
    - Tufts: Medical School Nicholson Lecture, 1994-05-02; MS247.001.002.00004.00031 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940502-A to 940502-B
    - Tufts Solo Sackler Bldg, 1994-05-15; MS247.001.002.00004.00032 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940515
    - Admis. Open House and Jumbofest, 1994-04-19; MS247.001.002.00004.00033 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940419-A to 940419-G
    - International Parents and Students Packard Hall, 1994-05-21; MS247.001.002.00004.00034 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940521-F to 940521-I
      Eleanor Short
    - Arts & Sciences 2nd JFK Dance, 1994-11-05; MS247.001.002.00004.00035 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941105-A to 941105-H
    - Dental Wide Open, 1994-09-27; MS247.001.002.00004.00036 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940927-A to 940927-H
    - Tufts Dental Hirsch Clinic Dedication, 1994-09-29; MS247.001.002.00004.00037 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940929-A to 940929-E
    - Tufts Arlene Rattner, 1994-06-27; MS247.001.002.00004.00038 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940627-A to 940627-C
      Arlene Rattner
    - Sunday Evening Engineering Dinner, 1994-10-22; MS247.001.002.00004.00039 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941022-A to 941022-B
    - Football 120th Anniversary, 1994-10-22; MS247.001.002.00004.00040 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941022-X to 941022-Z
    - Medical Student Assn., 1994-10-21; MS247.001.002.00004.00041 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941021-A to 941021-B
    - Tufts: Yankee Dental, 1994-01-21; MS247.001.002.00004.00042 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940121-R to 940121-Z
      Maria Gove
    - Emergency Thanksgiving Shot " dumb rooms", 1994-11-22; MS247.001.002.00004.00043 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941122
      Krishnamunthy
    - Tufts: BSOT Portraits, 1994-04-04; MS247.001.002.00004.00044 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940404-A to 940404-B
    - Tufts: Dental Comeback, 1994-11-04; MS247.001.002.00004.00045 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941104-A to 941104-B
    - Tufts: Granoff Family Hillel, 1994-12-04; MS247.001.002.00004.00046 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941204-A to 941204-O, 941204-Z
  - Tufts Volume 9 930122 to 930831, 1993-01-22 -- 1993-08-31; MS247.001.002.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - International Student Reception, 1993-08-30; MS247.001.002.00005.00001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930830-A to 930830-E
      Eli Short
    - Dental Student Alumni Comeback, 1993-08-30; MS247.001.002.00005.00002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930830-Z to 930830-Y
    - Drug study portrait of Jean Monehan, 1993-08-25; MS247.001.002.00005.00003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930825-A
    - Werner Chaison, 1993-06-04; MS247.001.002.00005.00004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930604-A to 930604-B
    - B-H are left Color Neg, 1993-05-27; MS247.001.002.00005.00005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930527-A
    - Tufts Commencement, 1993-05-23; MS247.001.002.00005.00006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930523-A to 930523-E
    - Tufts Pre Commencement Events Intl. Parents, recreation etc, 1993-05-22; MS247.001.002.00005.00007 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930522-A to 930522-M
      Gittleman
    - Charles Tufts Society Luncheon, 1993-05-21; MS247.001.002.00005.00008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930521-A to 930521-F
      Tom Hunt
    - Carole Boulter's Medical Awards Dinner, 1993-05-19; MS247.001.002.00005.00009 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930519-A to 930519-I
      School of Medicine; Carole Boulter
    - Center for the Study of Drugs, 1993-05-11; MS247.001.002.00005.00010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930511-A to 930511-B
    - Dental 125th Tufts Homecoming, 1993-05-01; MS247.001.002.00005.00011 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930501-A to 930501-HH
    - Tufts Employee Recognition, 1993-04-28; MS247.001.002.00005.00012 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930428-A to 930428-D
    - Tufts DiBiaggio Inauguration, 1993-04-25; MS247.001.002.00005.00013 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930425-A to 930425-JJ
    - Olin Reception for prospective students, 1993-04-20; MS247.001.002.00005.00014 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930420-A to 930420-B
    - Tufts Medical 100th, 1993-04-14; MS247.001.002.00005.00015 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930414-A to 930414-ZZ, 930414-AAA to 930414-JJJ
    - Tufts Shapiro Awards, 1993-04-13; MS247.001.002.00005.00016 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930413-A to 930413-B
      Liz Toupin
    - Tufts Parents Day, 1993-03-26; MS247.001.002.00005.00017 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930326-A to 930326-H
    - Center for Drug Study, 1993-02-22; MS247.001.002.00005.00018 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930222-A to 930222-L
    - Tufts Yankee Dental, 1993-01-22; MS247.001.002.00005.00019 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      930122-A to 930122-I
  - Tufts 1993, MS247.001.003.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 2nd Dance at MFA, Arts & Sciences Dinner Dance black tie, 1993-11-06; MS247.001.003.00001.00001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931106-A to 931106-L
    - Dean Frank Loew Bldg. Dedication, 1993-10-08; MS247.001.003.00001.00002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931008-A to 931008-M
      Frank Loew; Celeste Mahoney
    - Captain's Gate Dedication, 1993-10-30; MS247.001.003.00001.00003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931030-A to 931030-G
    - Health Sciences Dinner Dance, 1993-10-30; MS247.001.003.00001.00004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931030-O to 931030-Z
    - Medford Parent's Weekend, 1993-10-16; MS247.001.003.00001.00005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931016-A to 931016-P
    - Miss Saigon, 1993-09-30; MS247.001.003.00001.00006 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      930930-A to 930930-E
    - New England Colleges Fund, 1993-11-03; MS247.001.003.00001.00007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931103-A to 931103-G
      Nora Hall
    - Ellie Short, Tom Hunt Lunch, 1993-11-03; MS247.001.003.00001.00008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931103-X to 931103-Z
    - Tufts Medical Parents Weekend, 1993-10-23; MS247.001.003.00001.00009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931023-A to 931023-G
      School of Medicine; Ellie Short; Janice
    - Dental Wide Open, 1993-09-27; MS247.001.003.00001.00010 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      930927-A to 930927-H
    - Fitness Center Dedication, 1993-10-29; MS247.001.003.00001.00011 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931029-A to 931029-H
    - BSOT: Occupational Therapy 75th Anniversary, 1993-10-29; MS247.001.003.00001.00012 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931029-W to 931029-Z
    - Tufts: Biology Brochure, 1993-10-27; MS247.001.003.00001.00013 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931027-A to 931027-R
    - Opening of President's House, 1993-11-05; MS247.001.003.00001.00014 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931105-A to 931105-D
    - Wright / Gordon, 1993-11-04; MS247.001.003.00001.00015 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931104-F
    - Nutcracker, 1993-12-22; MS247.001.003.00001.00016 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931222-A to 931222-C
    - Wright & Gordon Sci Tech Dedication, 1993-11-04; MS247.001.003.00001.00017 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931104-A to 931104-E
    - Cousen's Gym, 1993-10-02; MS247.001.003.00001.00018 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      931102-A to 931102-B
  - Jean Mayer's Farewell, 1992-11-07; MS247.001.003.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    921107-A to 921107-Z, 921107AA to 921107VV
  - Tufts Volume 8 920123 to 921119, 1992-01-23 -- 1992-11-19; MS247.001.003.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Tufts: Environmental Eng. Portraits, 1992-11-06; MS247.001.003.00003.00001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      921106-W to 921106-Z
    - Tufts Hillel, 1992-10-26; MS247.001.003.00003.00002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      921026-A to 921026-B
    - Olin Donors Scholarship, 1992-10-24; MS247.001.003.00003.00003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      921024-A to 921024-F
    - Tufts Solo, 1992-10-07; MS247.001.003.00003.00004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      921007
    - Parents Weekend at Tufts, 1992-10-03; MS247.001.003.00003.00005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      921003-A to 921003-T
    - Tufts Club @ Phantom of the Opera, 1992-10-02; MS247.001.003.00003.00006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      921002-A to 921002-D
    - Dental Wide Open, 1992-09-16; MS247.001.003.00003.00007 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920916-A to 920916-L
    - Tufts T.U.D.C & FDA head, 1992-09-14; MS247.001.003.00003.00008 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920914-A to 920914-K
    - Vet Frank Loew's 10th Anniversary, 1992-09-12; MS247.001.003.00003.00009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920912-A to 920912-J
    - Tufts: Holocaust Exhibit, 1992-09-09; MS247.001.003.00003.00010 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920909-A to 920909-D
    - Dental Student Alumni Picnic, 1992-08-28; MS247.001.003.00003.00011 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920828 A to 920828-C
      School of Dental Medicine; Maria Gove; Nark Gonthier
    - Olin Bldg, 1992-07-23; MS247.001.003.00003.00012 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920723-A to 920723-D
    - Tony Blackett Downtown Campus Bldg Plan, 1992-07-14; MS247.001.003.00003.00013 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920714-A to 920714-D
    - Tufts Sackler Catalog, 1992-06-24; MS247.001.003.00003.00014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920624-A to 920624-H
    - Tufts Med retire emergency shot fro Harry Marshall, 1992-06-22; MS247.001.003.00003.00015 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920622
      School of Medicine; Harry Marshall
    - Peggy Newell, 1992-06-17; MS247.001.003.00003.00016 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920617-A to 920617-D
    - Medical Alumni, 1992-05-30; MS247.001.003.00003.00017 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920530-A to 920530-Y
    - Hosmer Dedication, 1992-05-20; MS247.001.003.00003.00018 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920520-A to 920520-C
    - Charles Tufts Society Luncheon, 1992-05-16; MS247.001.003.00003.00019 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920516-A to 920516-F
      P. Schweitzer
    - School of Medicine Senior Awards Dinner Dance, 1992-05-13; MS247.001.003.00003.00020 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920513-A to 920513-K
    - Drug Study Annual Meeting Sackler, 1992-05-11; MS247.001.003.00003.00021 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920511-A to 920511-H
      Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences; Barbara Richard
    - Tufts: Distinguished Service Awards, 1992-04-25; MS247.001.003.00003.00022 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920425-A to 920425-H
    - 10 year Employee luncheon, 1992-04-22; MS247.001.003.00003.00023 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920422-A to 920422-B
    - 25 year Employee luncheon w/ Mayer, 1992-04-17; MS247.001.003.00003.00024 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920417
    - 920411 I to V, 1992-04-11; MS247.001.003.00003.00025 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920411 I to V
    - Tufts Dental Alum, 1992-04-11; MS247.001.003.00003.00026 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920411-A to 920411-Z
    - Tufts Med Students Dinner Dance, 1992-04-10; MS247.001.003.00003.00027 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920410-P to 920410-R
    - Doctor Murray Gavel Dental, 1992-04-10; MS247.001.003.00003.00028 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920410-S to 920410-Z
    - Tufts Dental Parents, 1992-04-03; MS247.001.003.00003.00029 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920403-A to 920403-D
    - Tufts: Accreditation Committee, 1992-03-05; MS247.001.003.00003.00030 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920305-A to 920305-B
    - Tufts: Blackett / Roberto, 1992-02-02; MS247.001.003.00003.00031 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920202-A to 920202-F
    - " Dr. Less" Tufts Dental, 1992-01-31; MS247.001.003.00003.00032 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920131-A to 920131-F
    - Tufts: Yankee Dental, 1992-01-23; MS247.001.003.00003.00033 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      920123-A to 920123-G
  - Tufts 1995, MS247.001.003.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Vet Comeback, 1995-09-09; MS247.001.003.00004.00001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950909-A to 950909-H
    - Tufts Admissions Catalog, 1995-01-19; MS247.001.003.00004.00002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950119-A to 950119-O
    - Tufts Club, 1995-10-09; MS247.001.003.00004.00003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951009-A to 951009-C
    - Tufts Food, 1995-04-12; MS247.001.003.00004.00004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950412-A to 950412-B
    - International Students & Sol Gittleman Reception, 1995-05-19; MS247.001.003.00004.00005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950519-A to 950519-L
    - Tufts Dental Overseers, 1995-04-28; MS247.001.003.00004.00006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950428-Z
    - Tufts Medical Alumni Weekend / World Trade Center & Sackler, 1995-05-06; MS247.001.003.00004.00007 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950506-A to 950506-O
    - Tufts Lower Mills for Spectroscopy Kenn'y Diet Bench Set up, 1995-06-30; MS247.001.003.00004.00008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950630-A to 950630-J
    - Tufts Chemistry, 1995-05-12; MS247.001.003.00004.00009 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950512-A to 950512-P
    - Tufts Chemistry Dept Wrap up of Dilarco & Walt, 1995-06-14; MS247.001.003.00004.00010 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950614-A to 950614-E
    - C-Fast, 1995-06-30; MS247.001.003.00004.00011 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950630-D
    - Tufts Dental Alumni Weekend, 1995-04-29; MS247.001.003.00004.00012 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950429-A to 950429-N
    - Center for Study of Drug Dev. Am. Academy User fee Forum, 1995-05-18; MS247.001.003.00004.00013 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950518-A to 950518-E
    - Tufts Dental: Massler Operatories, 1995-02-02; MS247.001.003.00004.00014 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950202-A to 950202-E
    - Fletcher Catige, 1995-05-08; MS247.001.003.00004.00015 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950508-A to 950508-I
      Barbara Fennessey; Paul Bauer
    - Overseers Luncheon at D:B, 1995-05-02; MS247.001.003.00004.00016 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950502-A to 950502-D
    - Tufts Steve Tisch, 1995-03-03; MS247.001.003.00004.00017 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950303-A to 950303-C
    - Tufts Fletcher, 1995-03-31; MS247.001.003.00004.00018 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950331-A to 950331-D
    - Tufts Senior Awards Solo, 1995-04-22; MS247.001.003.00004.00019 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950422
    - Bay Tower Earling, 1995; MS247.001.003.00004.00020 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Tufts: Epic 10th Anniversary, 1995-03-05; MS247.001.003.00004.00021 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950305-A to 950305-B
    - Tufts Dental Parents, 1995-05-05; MS247.001.003.00004.00022 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950505-X to 950505-Z
      Ellie Short; Janice Di Perna
    - Tufts: Sackler, 1995-06-09; MS247.001.003.00004.00023 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950609-E 950609-G
    - Tufts: Fletcher Admiral Kramek for Pfalsgraff solo, 1995-02-20; MS247.001.003.00004.00024 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950220
    - Charles Tufts Society Luncheon, 1995-05-19; MS247.001.003.00004.00025 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950519-A to 950519-E
    - Tufts: Art Museum Medical, 1995-05-05; MS247.001.003.00004.00026 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950505-A to 950505-E
    - Tufts: Admissions Open House :Admits Day", 1995-04-21; MS247.001.003.00004.00027 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950421-A to 950421-G
      Ellie Short
    - Library Construction Photos, 1995; MS247.001.003.00004.00028 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Tufts: Fletcher, 1995-05-08; MS247.001.003.00004.00029 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950508-J to 950508-L
    - Announcement of New Neurosciences Dept, 1995-09-12; MS247.001.003.00004.00030 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950512-A to 950512-C
      Barbara Talamo
    - Tufts Dental Foreign Students Graduation, 1995-11-17; MS247.001.003.00004.00031 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951117
    - Tufts Jumbo Club Smoker!, 1995-10-27; MS247.001.003.00004.00032 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951027-A to 951027-D
    - Tufts: Japan Luncheon Solo, 1995-10-13; MS247.001.003.00004.00033 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951013
      Laurie Eshlem
    - Tufttonia's Day Jumbofest, 1995-04-21; MS247.001.003.00004.00034 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950421-V to 950421-Z
    - Parent's Weekend, 1995-10-14; MS247.001.003.00004.00035 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951014-A to 951014-O
    - Tufts Case Statements, 1995-09-26; MS247.001.003.00004.00036 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950926-A to 950926-R
    - Tufts "Teddy" Shapiro Awards, 1995-04-13; MS247.001.003.00004.00037 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950413-A to 950413-C
      Sheila Driscoll
    - Fletcher Christina Shelly (State Dept) gives Chas. Francis Adams Lecture, 1995-04-14; MS247.001.003.00004.00038 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950414
    - Yankee Dental Dean Johansen's Last, 1995-01-20; MS247.001.003.00004.00039 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950120-A to 950120-G
    - Honorary Degree Anson Chan, 1995-09-07; MS247.001.003.00004.00040 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950907-A to 950907-O
      Karen Bailey
    - Board meeting at office, 1995-05-09; MS247.001.003.00004.00041 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950509-A to 950509-C
    - Tufts Commencement, 1995-05-20; MS247.001.003.00004.00042 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950520-A to 950520-O
    - Fletcher Fed Lady Cathy Mennihan, 1995-11-30; MS247.001.003.00004.00043 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951130-A to 951130-B
    - Fletcher Leadership, 1995-11-30; MS247.001.003.00004.00044 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951130-Y to 951130-Z
    - Dean Johansen Farewell, 1995-06-02; MS247.001.003.00004.00045 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950602-A to 950602-J
    - Dental Staff Goodbye to Dean Johansen, 1995-05-04; MS247.001.003.00004.00046 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950504-A to 950504-C
    - Sackler Goodbye to Dean Maddoff, 1995-10-25; MS247.001.003.00004.00047 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951025-A to 951025-G
    - Tufts Sackler, 1995-06-09; MS247.001.003.00004.00048 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950609-A to 950609-C
    - Fletcher Welcome Dean Galvin Luncheon, 1995-05-01; MS247.001.003.00004.00049 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950501-A to 950501-D
    - Tufts Foreign Students, 1995-11-06; MS247.001.003.00004.00050 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951106-A to 951106-B
      Jane Ettish Andrews
    - Adolf Theis Honorary Degree, 1995-11-06; MS247.001.003.00004.00051 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951106-A to 951106-H
    - Tufts Ionis Engineers Group solo, 1995-11-27; MS247.001.003.00004.00052 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951127
    - Cindy at Dr Rosenberg's USDA, 1995-07-26; MS247.001.003.00004.00053 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950726-A to 950726-B
    - Tufts Summer School Chem solo, 1995-07-04; MS247.001.003.00004.00054 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950704
    - Bill Richardson & External Funding Seminar of Mel Bernstein, 1995-12-04; MS247.001.003.00004.00055 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      951204-A to 951204-F
      Bill Richardson
    - Ioannis Miaoulis Tufts Engineering, 1995-04-24; MS247.001.003.00004.00056 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      950424-A to 950424-J
      Ioannis Miaoulis
  - Valery Giscard D'estainge, 1996-02-08; MS247.001.003.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    960208-A to 960208-Q
    negatives (photographic); contact sheets
  - Tisch Library Dedication, 1996-10-09; MS247.001.003.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    961009-A to 961009-U
    negatives (photographic); digital images
  - Tufts 1996, MS247.001.004.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Charles Tufts Society Luncheon, 1996-05-16; MS247.001.004.00001.00001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960516-A to 960516-G
    - Honorary Degree Dinner Gifford House, 1996-05-18; MS247.001.004.00001.00002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960518-R to 960518-Z
    - Parents Weekend at Tufts, 1996-10-01; MS247.001.004.00001.00003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      961001-A to 961001-Q
    - Health Sciences Dinner FAO Schwartz, 1996-10-26; MS247.001.004.00001.00004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      961026-A to 961026-I
    - Fares Lecture James Baker, 1996-10-30; MS247.001.004.00001.00005 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      961030-A to 961030-O
    - Tufts Vet Kohnstamm Conf room dedication, 1996-05-06; MS247.001.004.00001.00006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960506-A to 960506-D
    - Tufts Christie's NYC, 1996-02-22; MS247.001.004.00001.00007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960222-A to 960222-J
    - Dental Crowd Frame solo, 1996-01-26; MS247.001.004.00001.00008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960126-G
    - Dental Overseers solo, 1996-04-26; MS247.001.004.00001.00009 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960426
    - Distinguished Service Awards, 1996-05-04; MS247.001.004.00001.00010 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960504-A to 960504-F
    - Tufts: Doku Dinner, 1996-05-14; MS247.001.004.00001.00011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960514-A to 960514-K
    - Fletcher Catalog Testimonials, 1996-04-16; MS247.001.004.00001.00012 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960416-A to 960416-O
    - Toni Snow's Center for Study of Drug Development, 1996-02-27; MS247.001.004.00001.00013 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960227-A to 960227-D
    - Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1996-05-20; MS247.001.004.00001.00014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960520-A to 960520-E
    - Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development 20th Anniversary, 1996-05-01; MS247.001.004.00001.00015 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960501-A to 960501-C
    - Dental Alumni Reunion Committee Photo solo, 1996-05-29; MS247.001.004.00001.00016 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960529
    - Tufts Club: 10th Anniversary, 1996-04-25; MS247.001.004.00001.00017 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960425-A to 960425-D
    - Tour of Curtis Hall GTE Visit, 1996-02-21; MS247.001.004.00001.00018 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960221
      Paul Mischler
    - Shapiro Awards, 1996-04-18; MS247.001.004.00001.00019 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960418-A to 960418-B
    - NYNEX with Ioannis Engineering, 1996-03-25; MS247.001.004.00001.00020 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960325
    - Tufts Dental: Alumnae Portraits, 1996-06-03; MS247.001.004.00001.00021 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960603
    - 960518-A to 960518-D, 1996-05-18; MS247.001.004.00001.00022 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960518-A to 960518-D
    - Rocky's Smoker, 1996-10-18; MS247.001.004.00001.00023 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      961018-A to 961018-D
    - Tufts: Vet Comeback, 1996-09-07; MS247.001.004.00001.00024 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960907-A to 960907-M
    - Tisch Library, 1996; MS247.001.004.00001.00025 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Nils Wessell
    - Tisch Library, 1996; MS247.001.004.00001.00026 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      photographic prints
    - Tufts: Packard Society Dinner Dance, 1996-11-02; MS247.001.004.00001.00027 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      961102-A to 961102-E
    - Tufts: Packard Society Dinner Dance, 1996-11-02; MS247.001.004.00001.00028 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - French Student Diplomas Solo, 1996-10-31; MS247.001.004.00001.00029 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      961031
    - Tufts Club: Fitness Center Brochure, 1996-10-02; MS247.001.004.00001.00030 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      961002-A to 961002-B
    - Sackler Medical Commencement, 1996-05-19; MS247.001.004.00001.00031 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960519-A to 960519-P
    - Tufts "Pre Pops" Alumni @ DiBiaggio's, 1996-05-16; MS247.001.004.00001.00032 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      960516-U to 960516-Z
  - Tufts 1996 Volume 2, MS247.001.004.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Dental Burke, 1996-09-29; MS247.001.004.00002.00001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960929-A to 960929-H